Modular Library
Modular Library is a resource library that helps you quickly use and combine clothing items.
Right-click on the title on the left side of the page and click on the Modular Library.
You can see that the Modular Library has been opened.
If you are new here, you can see that there are three folders for children, men, and women.
Double-click to enter the next folder.
Here are some basic clothing types.
If you are new here, you can see that there are basic shoes, make-up, shirt, jacket, polo shirt.
Double-click again to open Basic Sheets.
After entering the specific style, you can see that the clothing has been divided into several large modules.
Each module has a rich array of items for you to switch.
Once you have selected it,
you need to click on the Modular Library.
Here are all the modules you need.
Press Shift A to hide the virtual model.
Using the clothing created by the Modular Library,
the sewing relationship between the modules can be automatically identified.
Press B to display the sewing line.
You will find that the sewing line has been automatically created.
Use the button to simulate,
we got a piece of metal clothing quickly through the Modular Library.
You can quickly change the clothing here.
You can freely combine it to the clothing you want.
When you double-click to switch a particular item,
the item in the previous module will be replaced and disappeared.
So please save each piece of clothes in a timely manner to protect the safety of the file.
To avoid the presence of more pieces of clothes in the scene, some panels will be replaced by hand.
Continue to modify the clothing effect you want on the created basic clothing.
Here we change the sleeves of the skirt into medium sleeves.
After modifying the satisfied effect, click on the plus sign in this column.
Press Shift, select two sleeves, press Enter to confirm.
Confirm the panel, then confirm the sewing relationship.
This self-defined part has been successfully stored.
You can quickly use it through the module library in the future.
You can create various self-defined parts and styles through the small plus signs in the upper right corner of each layer.
Press the upper label to return to the last layer.
Each layer can be created through the small plus sign to create a specific classification folder.
For example, now we have made a set of women's hanbok and want to add it to the module library.
So let's go to Woman first.
Click on the small plus sign to create a new category named Hanbok.
Enter the Hanbok category.
Click on the small plus sign to add a style named Hanbok 1.
Select Hanbok 1.
Click on the small plus sign to add the required part type.
For example, this outfit is made up of front, back, sleeves, and collar.
Then we need to add these four parts.
Tips 2.
Reglan refers to the clothes with a shoulder-in-shoulder style.
The shoulder-in-shoulder style is more special due to the sewing relationship.
It is impossible to identify and create a sewing line with most clothes.
So the parts are listed separately.
If you don't have a shirt with a shoulder-in-shoulder style, don't choose Reglan.
After adding all the necessary parts,
click on the small star next to the top of the small plus sign to automatically model and draw a label.
You can see that each module is automatically identified.
Check if there is a mistake in identification.
Click on the small Families to add part effects and Confirm.
Click on the small Sachein and type the part image.
Click shift stupid and add paper with much 170 body parts and confirm by pressing the Enter key.
Check if there is a mistake and add paper with much 170 body parts and confirm.
After confirming all, click on Add, and you can see that this Hanfu is stored in a patterned way, and now all of its parts can be used quickly.
You can continue to add various styles to create your own patterned resource library.
Tip 3. In addition to the extra-partition embroidery style mentioned earlier, most of the parts can be cross-styled and automatically create a sewing line.
You can use your imagination.
Create various interesting fashion combinations.
See you in the next video. Bye bye.